♪Come closer♪
اقترب ♪
♪Be more intimate♪
♪ كن أكثر حميمية
♪Tell me if I am tempted♪
♪ قل لي إن كنت أغوى
♪The moment you and I looked at each other♪
♪ في اللحظة التي نظرت فيها أنا وأنت إلى بعضنا البعض
♪We were both tempted♪
كلانا أغوى
♪Remember how shy you were♪
♪ تذكر كم كنت خجولًا ♪
♪That day♪
♪ ذلك اليوم ♪
♪Sweet memories♪
♪ ذكريات حلوة ♪
♪Please be more♪
♪ من فضلك كن اكثر
♪How lucky I am to have you♪
♪ كم أنا محظوظ لوجودك ♪
♪So sweet♪
♪ حلوة جدا ♪
=My Naughty Assistant=
= مساعدي المشاغب =
=Episode 10=
= الحلقة 10 =
Mr. Xing.
السيد شينغ.
The lawyer is here.
المحامي هنا.
Ms. Wang.
السيدة وانغ.
It's clearly stated on the contract.
هو مذكور بوضوح في العقد.
We don't have a big chance
ليس لدينا فرصة كبيرة
to win it.
للفوز بها.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Enchen.
يملأ
This contract for reasonable avoidance of individual income tax,
هذا العقد للتهرب المعقول من ضريبة الدخل الفردي ،
did you sign it?
هل وقعت عليه
Yes.
نعم.
You're always dozy.
أنت دائما غاضب.
And you even have no basic knowledge of the law?
وليس لديك حتى معرفة أساسية بالقانون؟
It's a dual contract.
إنه عقد مزدوج.
Do you know how bad it is?
هل تعلم كم هو سيء؟
We will be criminally responsible.
سنكون مسؤولين جنائيا.
I signed it.
وقعت عليه.
Not your problem.
ليست مشكلتك.
Lawyer,
محامي،
I signed it.
وقعت عليه.
It has nothing to do with Enchen.
لا علاقة له بـ Enchen.
I will bear all the legal consequences.
سوف أتحمل جميع التبعات القانونية.
It's not a joke.
انها ليست مزحة.
I won't take on the case.
لن أتولى القضية.
Sorry.
آسف.
Lawyer.
محامي.
Enchen.
يملأ
I...
أنا...
I'll see what we can do.
سأرى ما يمكننا القيام به.
There's got to be a way.
يجب أن يكون هناك طريقة.
Linda, come in.
ليندا ، تعال.
Hand over your work with Linda.
سلم عملك مع ليندا.
Leave me alone.
اتركني وحدي.
You go back.
تعود.
I...
أنا...
Duoduo, what happened?
Duoduo ، ماذا حدث؟
Jiawei.
جياوي.
I messed up.
لقد أخفقت.
That man gave you trouble?
لقد تسبب لك هذا الرجل في المتاعب؟
I will fix him.
سوف أصلحه.
It was all my fault.
كان كل خطأي.
I didn't read it carefully.
لم أقرأها بعناية.
I shouldn't have signed that contract.
ما كان يجب أن أوقع هذا العقد.
I was going to pick up someone at the airport
كنت على وشك اصطحاب شخص ما في المطار
when it was given to me.
عندما أعطيت لي.
And Linda wasn't there that day.
ولم تكن ليندا هناك في ذلك اليوم.
I didn't want to be late,
لا أريد أن أتأخر ،
so I signed it without consideration.
لذلك وقعت عليه دون اعتبار.
I'm here for you.
أنا هنا من أجلك.
I'll help you figure out what to do.
سأساعدك في معرفة ما يجب القيام به.
♪How many times in my life♪
♪ كم مرة في حياتي ♪
♪I am destined♪
أنا مقدر ♪
♪To meet you and fall in love with you♪
♪ لمقابلتك والوقوع في حبك
♪In my finest age♪
♪ في خيرة عمري ♪
♪It's a pity♪
♪ إنه لأمر مؤسف
♪That we are not together in this life♪
بأننا لسنا معًا في هذه الحياة
♪But still, thank you♪
♪ لكن مع ذلك ، شكرًا لك ♪
♪For letting me♪
♪ لسماحك لي ♪
♪Walk into your world♪
♪ امش في عالمك ♪